Redmond will destroy you.
I only came here
today out of pity, Severin.
I wanted to give
you a way out.
Save it.
I'm not ending the engagement.
I'd love to see how you plan to make me regret it.
Don't come crying to me.
Whatever.
Now get out of my house.
Fine!
Then we do the wedding.
I'll make sure the entire city watches you crawl
on your knees and
beg me for mercy!
Damn it!
No one on
this entire continent has
ever made me
regret a damn thing.
Let's see what you've got.
Cassia.
My lord.
Three days from now
I will hold my wedding.
Send words to every major power cross Golantis.
I want them all
in attendance.
The one the Sovereign Sanctum
signed with the Scott family,
have it
read aloud at the wedding.
As you command, my lord.
Every name that
matters will be there.
Severin,
we need to come
back to House Carter now!
Your father's dying.